I'm back at the Obscene in Karlsruhe, an adult trade fair with kinky fashion and toys.
So we're going to have a look around and see what old friends we meet, what new things we're going to discover.
So let's go. Come along.
What is the young kid with the world at her toes?
I'm giving you my word now
There's panic on the street
That what I've done is hopeless
And my dreams are at sea
But my mother never doubted
My passion or love
I'll finish what I started
It's in my blood
I said goodbye
I said goodbye twice
We say hello to the world
And I'll begin what I came to start
When I said goodbye
I didn't know why and perhaps I never will
It isn't easy when forgiveness is the pill
It takes my patience but when all is said and done
I wish you'd see me
And be so proud of who I've become
I'm giving you my word now
There's panic on the street
That what I've done is hopeless
And my dreams are obscene
But my mother never doubted
My passion or love
I'll finish what I started
It's in my blood
I said goodbye
Goodbye twice, we say hello to the world
And I'll begin what I came to start
I said goodbye
I said goodbye twice, we say hello to the world
And I'll begin what I came to start
When I said goodbye
I'm giving you my word now
There's panic on the street
Like what I've done is hopeless
And my dreams are obscene
But my mother never doubted
My passion or love
I'll finish what I've started
It's in my blood
I said goodbye
Twice we said hello
To the world
And I'll begin what I came to start
I said goodbye
Twice we say hello to the world
And I'll begin what I came to start when I said goodbye
I'm giving you my word now
There's panic on the street
Like what I've done is hopeless
And my dreams are obscene
But my mother never doubted
My passion or love